A Guide to the Papers of the Proctor of the University of Virginia, (Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough), 1817-1828
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- And[re]w Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:177)
- And[re]w Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:178)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 7, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:179)
- Cha[rle]s L. Bankhead to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:180)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:181)
- Carter B. Page to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:182)
- And[re]w Smith to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 June 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:183)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 18, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:184)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 June 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:185)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Alex[ander] Garrett 1821 July 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:186)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:187)
- And[re]w Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:188)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 19, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:189)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 26, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:190)
- Carter B. Page to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:191)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 July 31, ALS, 2 p. with address, dockets (Box-folder 2:192)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 [August 2], ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:193)
- Armistead Long to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 August 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:194)
- Carter B. Page to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 August 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:195)
- Lyman Peck and Malcom F. Crawford: contract for carpentry 1821 August 10, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:196)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 August 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:197)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 August 20, ALS, 2 p. with receipt, docket. (Box-folder 2:198)
- D. C. Hutchison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 August 21, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:199)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 August 30, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:200)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:201)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:202)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 4, ALS, 1 p. with receipt, docket (Box-folder 2:203)
- Ch[arle]s D. Gardner to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:204)
- Carter B. Page to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 September 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:205)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:206)
- R. & J. McCulloch to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 10, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:207)
  On verso, calculations between "end walls"
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 15, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:208)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:209)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1821 September 18, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:210)
- Richard Ware: receipt, attached to account: University with Richard Ware, 1820 March 30 - 1821 September 19 1821 September 19, ADS. 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:211)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 September 26, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:212)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 October 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:213)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 October 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:214)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 October 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:215)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 October 25, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:216)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1899] 1821 November 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:217)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1900] 1821 November 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:218)
- Andrew Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 November 10, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:219)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 November 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:220)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough-receipt [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1903] 1821 November 22, DS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:221)
- Alex[ander] Garrett to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 November 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:222)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 November 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:223)
- Cha[rle]s L. Bankhead to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 December 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:224)
- Alex[ander] Galt to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 December 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:225)
- E[dmund] Bacon to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 December 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:226)
- E[dmund] Bacon to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1821 December 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:227)
- R[obley] Dunglison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough c. 1821, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 2:228)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1912] [1821], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:229)
- Papers related to glazing, carpentry, plastering, painting, and stonework, including contract proposals submitted by Abiah B. Thorn and Nathaniel Chamberlain, John Gorman, John Bowles, Abner B. Hawkins, and Edward Evans 1821, ADS, pntd. 9 items. (Box-folder 2:230)
- Questions to W[illiam] Thackara & E[dward] Evans re: the price of plastering 1821, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:231)
- Estimates of dormitory alterations c. 1821, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:232)
- Extract of J[ohn]; H[artwell] Cocke's contract with T. Whitelaw c. 1821, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 2:233)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1821, ANS. 169 items. (Box-folder 2:234)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1928] 1822 February 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:235)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 February 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:236)
- D[abney] Cosby to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 March 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:237)
- B[rockenbrough] & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 March 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:238)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee: contract for Pavilion ornamentation, with attached invoice 1822 March 18, ADS. 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:239)
- George Miller to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 March 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:240)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 April 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:241)
- Dabney Cosby to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough (receipt on verso) 1822 April 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:242)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough (receipt on verso) 1822 May 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:243)
- Statement by [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough]: voucher locations for his account, 1819 September 14 - 1822 May 14 [1822 May 14], AD, 8:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:244)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 June 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:245)
- Memorandum of the Committee of the Board of Visitors requesting financial accounts and recommending revised accounting procedures by the proctor and the accountant, signed by John H[artwell] Cocke and Joseph C[arrington] Cabell, with attached statements of account with Martin Dawson, 1822 September 9 - November 19 and 1822 November 23-27, receipted by Martin Dawson, 1823 June 5 1822 August 13, ADS draft. 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:246)
- Copy of memorandum in preceding item 1822 August 13, AD copy. 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:247)
- University to James Monroe 1822 August 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:248)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Angus McKay 1822 September 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:249)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to John Vowles 1822 September 12, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:250)
- Peter Johnston to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 September 16, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:251)
- C. L. Abraham to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - bill 1822 October 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:252)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with transcript, 2 p. [original in Jefferson Papes #TB-1949] 1822 October 11, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:253)
- Martin Dawson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with list of accounts 1822 October 15, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:254)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 November 13, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:255)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1953] [1822] November 21, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:256)
- List of vouchers for Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 's account (1820 March 20-1822 November 18) 1822 November 23, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:257)
- Bern[ar]d Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1822 December 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:258)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1956 [1822 December 19], ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:259)
- Peter Maverick to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #FC-3015-a] 1822 December 23, ALS, 1 p. with dockets (Box-folder 3:260)
- Bills and accounts 1822, ANS. 198 items. (Box-folder 3:261)
- Miscellaneous accounts 1822, AD. 3 items. (Box-folder 3:262)
  Drawing of Rotunda modillion by John Neilson removed from this folder and filed in Thomas Jefferson papers under date [1825 June/July]
- Miscellaneous receipts 1822, ANS. 105 items. (Box-folder 3:263)
- Rob[ert] Johnston to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 January 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:264)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1966] 1823 January 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:265)
- Abiah B. Thorn and Nath[anie]l Chamberlain: contract with Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough for laying brick for Rotunda 1823 March 8, ADS. 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:266)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson. Originally enclosed contract with Dinsmore & Neilson. [original in Jefferson Papers] 1823 March 11, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:267)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, enclosing [a copy of] a portion of a contract with James Dinsmore and John Neilson, attested by John M. Perry and Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1983 item 1] 1823 March 12, ALS / AD, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:268)
- [Thomas Jefferson] to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough (draft of preceding item) [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1983 item 2] 1823 March 12, AL draft. 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:269)
- Blackford, Arthur & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 March 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:270)
- Robert Johnston to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough (bill on verso) 1823 March 21, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:271)
- Thomas Jefferson's memorandum on the finances of the University; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson, "State of the finances Oct. 1823" [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1990] 1823 April 6, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:272)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Rector and [Board of] Visitors; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson. Originally enclosed contract with W[illia]m J. Coffee [original in Jefferson Papers] 1823 April 7, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:273)
- Anderson & Woodson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 April 9, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:274)
- Edw[ard] Anderson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, enclosing an account, 1821 April 23 - 1823 April 9, with attached authorization of payment to John M. Perry receipted by John M. Perry 1823 May 30 1823 April 10, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:275)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1823 April 14, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:276)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 April 19, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:277)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-1993] 1823 April 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:278)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with Brockenbrough & Harvie receipt, 1823 May 26, attached 1823 May 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:279)
- C[harles] Everett to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 May 4, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:280)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 May 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:281)
- Rob[ert] Johnston to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with invoice 1823 May 19, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:282)
- W[illiam] F. Micon to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 May 23, ALS, 4 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:283)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 June 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:284)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 June 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:285)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2006] 1823 June 16, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:286)
- Tho[ma]s B. Conway to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 June 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:287)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2007] 1823 June 20, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:288)
- John M. Perry to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with attached receipt 1823 June 26, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:289)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough: Memorandum on cost of marble capitals; 1823 July 3 -, AD,. (Box-folder 3:290)
- endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2013] 1823 August 26, . 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:)
- Cost of marble capitals 1823 July 3, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:291)
- Bern[ar]d Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 July 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:292)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough and J[oseph]; A[ntrim] to W[illia]m Thackara and E[dward] Evans 1823 July 16, ALS (copy). 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:293)
- Joseph C[arrington] Cabell to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 July 17, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:294)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 July 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:295)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with attached account, 1821 July 31-1823 July 25 1823 July 25, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:296)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 July 30, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:297)
- Joseph C[arrington] Cabell to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1823 August 7, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:298)
- Thomas Jefferson to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2017] 1823 August 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:299)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2019] 1823 August 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:300)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2018] 1823 August 11, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:301)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 August 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:302)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2021] 1823 September 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:303)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 September 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:304)
- Giacomo Raggi's contract to furnish bases for columns 1823 September 8, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:305)
- W[illiam] B. Phillips to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough (receipt on verso) 1823 September 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:306)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with receipt on verso, signed by Giacomo Raggi [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2024] [1823 September 17], ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:307)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2026] 1823 September 20, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:308)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 September 22, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:309)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough: Contract with Giacomo Raggi; copied by Thomas Jefferson. With correction, T.J. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2028] 1823 September, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:310)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 October 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:311)
- Martin Dawson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 October 4, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:312)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to John Mosby, with reply, 1823 November 26 assigning payment to Benjamin Mosby and receipt of B.M. dated 1823 December 2 1823 October 4, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:313)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with invoice, 1818 April 1-1823 October 6 1823 October 6, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:314)
- Edw[ar]d Evans to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough and J[oseph] Antrim 1823 October 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:315)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2031] 1823 November 2, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 3:316)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1823 November 13, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:317)
- Account of the University with A[biah] B. Thorn 1823 [November 14], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:318)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2033] 1823 November 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:319)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2034] 1823 November 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:320)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2036] 1823 November 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:321)
- Giacomo Raggi to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 December 18, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 3:322)
- Benjamin Blackford to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1823 December 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:323)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2038] 1823 December 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:324)
- Balance sheet of the University 1823 December 31, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:325)
- Calculation of the bricks for the Rotunda 1823, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:326)
- Cost of brickmaking 1823, AD, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:327)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 's copy of Thomas Jefferson's instructions for brick-laying and carpentry [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2044] c. 1823, AD (copy). 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 3:328)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1823, ANS. 188 items. (Box-folder 3:329)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2045] 1824 January 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:330)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 January 4, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:331)
- Rob[ert] Johnston to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with invoice 1824 January 16, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:332)
- E[dward] Evans to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 January 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:333)
- Thomas Nelson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 January 28, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:334)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 January 29, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:335)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 February 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:336)
- Wilson Bryan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 February 24, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:337)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2051] 1824 February 25, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:338)
- Balance sheet of the University 1824 February 28, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:339)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; note re: deduction within text by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2052] 1824 March 4, ALS, 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 4:340)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - estimate of income and expenses of the University from 1823 January 1-December 31 [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2053] 1824 March 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:341)
- Wilson Bryan to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 March 14, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:342)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 March 25, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:343)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 March 25, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:344)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson] re: unauthorized construction by Dinsmore & Neilson, with recommendation by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough Notation "disapproved" by Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2061] 1824 March 28, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:345)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: disapproval of Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 's suggestion and warning to Dinsmore & Neilson not to exceed authorized work [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2062] 1824 March 29, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:346)
- Thomas Nelson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 March 29, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:347)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson] (estimate of cost of Rotunda); endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2066] 1824 April 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:348)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 April 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:349)
- Plat of land north of the University acquired from Mr./Mrs. Daniel A. Piper 1824 April 8, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:350)
- Deed of land from Mary Garner to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, approved by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2068] 1824 April 9, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:351)